// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "What is full form of CSS?",
  answer: "Cascading Style Sheets",
  options: [
    "Cascading Security System",
    "Cyber Stict Sheets",
    "Cascading Style Sheets",
    "Cyber Security System"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "What can we change the background color of an element?",
  answer: "Background-color",
  options: [ 
    "Color",
    "Background-color",
    "Both A & B",
    "None of these"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "What tag do you use to directly write the style rules with a document found with the document's head?",
  answer: " <style>",
  options: [
    "CSS",
    "style",
    "Php",
    " Script"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "In an HTML page, Which of these tags is used for embedded CSS?",
  answer: "Script",
  options: [
    "DOCTYPE.html",
    "CSS",
    "Style",
    "Script"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "Who invented CSS?",
  answer: "Hakon Wium Lie",
  options: [
    "Sunder Pichai",
    "Hakon Wium Lie",
    "Ratan Tata",
    "Harry Potter"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "Translation softwares are known as?",
  answer: "Translation",
  options: [
    "Scripting",
    "Coding",
    "Translation",
    "Compiler "
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "When was CSS released?",
  answer: "1996",
  options: [
    "1994",
    "1995",
    "1996",
    "1997"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "In how many ways can CSS be written?",
  answer: "3",
  options: [
    "1",
    "2",
    "3",
    "4"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "Which HTML tag used to declare internal CSS?",
  answer: "style",
  options: [
    "Link",
    "Script",
    "Style",
    "None of these"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "Which of these specifies the type of list in CSS?",
  answer: "List-style-type",
  options: [
    "Ol",
    "List-style-type",
    "UL",
    "List"
  ]
},
// you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
// but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

//   {
//   numb: 6,
//   question: "Your Question is Here",
//   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
//   options: [
//     "Option 1",
//     "option 2",
//     "option 3",
//     "option 4"
//   ]
// },
];